creativeprooffice.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy :: Project Management Dashboard Software to Organize Your Work

Print this page.

## Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us.

At CreativePro Office we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

## Information that CreativePro Office Gathers and Collects

CreativePro Office gathers two types of information about users:

  1. Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions through the CreativePro Office account signup form, the CreativePro Office contact form and "Add Your Comments" form on the CreativePro Office blog.
  2. Information CreativePro Office gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site through Google Analytics. This information allows us to better tailor our content and services to our customers' needs.

## CreativePro Office Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

### Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

### CreativePro Office Account Registration

We request an email address from the user before they can access our member areas. This information must be gathered in order to assign each user a unique user account. A user account allows the user to upload and store resources (photos, text, messages) on the site for the purpose of organizing and managing projects, tasks, team members, calendars, and timesheets.

### CreativePro Office Contact Form

We request an email address from the user before submitting a contact request on the CreativePro Office website.

### Add Your Comments to the CreativePro Office Blog

We require that a name and email address be provided from the user before posting comments to the CreativePro Office blog.

## Children

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

## Usage tracking

CreativePro Office tracks user traffic patterns throughout the site by using Google Analytics and other proprietary tracking mechanisms. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. CreativePro Office does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

## Cookies

CreativePro Office uses cookies for user authentication during login, maintaining application state while the user is logged in, and keeping the time clock synchronized between individual page views while the user is logged in.

## Use of Information

CreativePro Office uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our website, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we do gather email addresses from our users. This information is only used to communicate to the user during the signup process, to provide customer support, to communicate with the user after the user has posted a comment on the CreativePro Office blog and distribution of opt-in email newsletters and promotions. CreativePro Office never shares newsletter mailing lists or individual email addresses with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for our customers.

CreativePro Office creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, we will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

## SECURITY

CreativePro Office operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. User account passwords are encryptet using the sha1 encryption algorithm with a random salt and cannot be decrypted.

## Opt-out Policy

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users.

## Your Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CreativePro Office. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If, at this time, you have concerns or questions about the CreativePro Office privacy policy, please email us at [info@CreativeProOffice.com](mailto:info@CreativeProOffice.com). 

**PleaseContact Support if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy.**
